Support for NPR comes from Moises, the
creative suite for musicians. Used by
over 75 million artists worldwide to
learn, create, and collaborate.
Available for phone, tablet, and
desktop.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I just searched you from the wound
you've [singing] been looking, [music]
you've been looking for.
I wish I would have known [singing] that
it was me.
Cuz even after all [music] this time, I
still wonder
why I can't move on
just the way you did so easily.
Don't want [singing] to know how I could
have just showed up where you are
tonight. If he's holding you
>> [singing and music]
>> so tight the way I did before.
I overdosed. [singing]
Should have known your love was a
drug. Now I can't get you out of
[singing and music] my
mind. Oh, it's such a shame.
We don't talk anymore.
>> [music]
>> We don't talk anymore.
We don't talk anymore like we
[singing and music] used to
do.
We don't love anymore.
What was all of it for?
Oh, we don't talk anymore like
[music and singing] we used to
do. I just hope you're lying next to
somebody who knows
You let me.
There must a good reason [singing] that
she's gone.
Every now and [music] then I think you
might want me to come show up at your
door. [singing]
But I'm just too afraid that I'll be
wrong.
Don't want [singing] to know [music] if
you're looking into it.
If you sold onto your soul
>> Wait, what?
>> like before
I overdosed. [music and singing]
Should have known your love was a lethal
Now I can't get you out of
[music and singing] my brain.
Whoa, it's such a shame
that we don't talk anymore.
>> We don't We [singing and music] don't
>> We don't talk anymore.
>> We don't We don't
>> We don't talk anymore like we
[singing and music] used to do.
We don't love anymore.
>> We don't We don't
>> What was [music and singing] all of it
for?
>> We don't We don't
>> We don't talk anymore like we used to
do.
Yeah.
>> Like
>> [music]
[music]
>> And [music] one more time.
>> [music]
>> Like
>> Y'all feeling good?
I said, are y'all feeling good?
>> [music]
>> It's not every day I don't sing with any
reverb, but I do it for Tiny Desk, okay?
>> [music]
>> Let's do a thing [singing] like a
[music]
[singing]
>> We out.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Thank [applause] you.
That's the word That's the version I
wish came out
originally.
You're going to hear a lot of jazz
chords, ladies and gentlemen.
By the way, if y'all know some of these
songs, you can
add to the choir here. It just makes me
sound better.
We're going to do this one a little
differently.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Run around, run around, run around and
throwing that dirt on my name
cuz you knew that I'd [singing] knew
that I'd knew that I'd call you up.
You can go around, go around, go around
[singing] every party in LA
cuz you knew that I'd knew that I'd knew
that I [singing] had me I wanted.
>> [music]
>> I know that trust is karma, perfume,
regret. [singing]
You got me thinking back when you were
mine.
>> [music]
>> And now I'm [singing] all up on you.
What you expect? You should not come
[music and singing] in on with me
tonight.
You just want attention.
[music and singing]
You don't want me.
Maybe you just see [music] the thought
of me with someone new. Yeah, you just
[singing] want attention.
I knew
>> [music]
>> from the start.
You're just making sure I never get it
over you.
>> [music]
>> You run around and run around and run
around throwing that dirt all on my
name.
>> [music]
>> Cuz you knew that I knew that I knew
that I knew that
Maybe another word, [music] another
word, another word ain't as significant
as you face
You already know, already
[singing and music] know, already know
that you want
I know that [singing] trust is karma
but pure regret
You got me thinking about when you were
mine.
Oh.
And now [music and singing] I'm all up
on you. What did you expect?
>> For what?
>> But you're not coming home with me
tonight.
Cuz you just want attention. You don't
want more.
Maybe you just [music] hate the thought
of me with someone new. Yeah, you just
want attention. I knew [music] from the
start.
You're just making sure I never get it
over you.
>> So, the bridge
>> [music]
>> What are you doing?
>> [singing]
What are you doing?
>> [music]
[singing]
>> What are you doing?
>> [music]
[singing]
>> I know that trust is karma but pure
regret [music and singing]
You got me thinking about when you were
mine.
>> [music]
>> And now [singing] I'm all up on you.
What did you expect?
You're not coming home with me tonight.
>> You just want attention. [music] You
don't want my heart.
Maybe [singing] you just want
Yeah, you just want attention.
You're [music and singing] just making
sure I'm never getting
over you,
over you.
>> [music and singing]
>> Yeah, you just want attention. [music]
I know you're from the start.
You're just making sure I'm never
over you.
>> [music]
[music]
[singing]
>> I like that.
A little [music] quieter though.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Yeah, right here.
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
[applause]
>> Thank you.
>> [applause]
>> I had a I'm not sick now. I had a cold a
couple weeks ago. So, I'm just I'm happy
I can hit these high notes.
Um wow, thank you Tiny Desk for
inviting me on here. I've I've always
dreamed of doing this and uh exactly
like this. I've heard these arrangements
in my head and uh I've been saving them
for this. So, thank you. Thank you NPR.
Thank you everybody. Um we're going to
do this one, which you might know in a
different key in a slightly different
arrangement.
You got like a nice [music] organ sound
on there there.
A lot of my music uh is
the chords are derived from church.
Cuz I'm very inspired by those chord
changes and
feels very like grounding.
And that's how I wrote [music] this
song.
I guess that I guess you could call this
is like the
>> [music]
>> original version of this song, not the
one that you hear on the radio.
>> [music]
[music]
>> It's been a long [singing] day [music]
without you, my friend.
And I'll tell you all about [singing] it
when I see you again.
We've come a long [singing]
way
from [music] where we began.
Oh, I'll tell [singing] you all
about it when I see you again. When
[singing] I see you
again.
Why'd she have [music and singing] to
leave so soon, yeah?
Why'd she have to go?
Why'd she have to leave me when
[singing]
I needed you the most?
I play it back over [singing] and over
and hear your last words.
I know you're in [singing] a better
place, but it's always going to hurt.
So, carry on. [singing and music]
Give me all the strength I need to carry
on.
It's been a long [singing and music]
day
without you, my friend.
And I'll tell you [singing] all about it
[music] when I see you again.
We've come a long way [singing]
from where [music] we began.
Oh, I'll [singing] tell you all about it
when I see you again. [singing]
When I see [music] you
again.
Oh.
>> [singing]
[music]
>> Oh.
>> [singing]
>> [music]
>> How do I breathe without
[music and singing]
you?
Feeling so cold.
I'll be waiting, [singing] waiting for
you [music] till the day you're home.
So, carry on.
>> [singing]
>> Give me all the strength I need to carry
[music] on.
So, [music] let the light guide
[singing]
your way.
Hold every [singing] memory as [music]
you go.
And every road [singing] you take
>> [music]
>> will always
[singing] lead you home.
>> [singing]
>> It's been a long [singing and music]
day
without [snorts] you, my friend.
And I'll tell you all [singing] about it
when I see you again.
We've come a [music] long
>> [singing]
>> way
from where we began.
>> [singing and music]
>> I'll tell you all about it when I see
you again.
When I see [singing and music]
>> [singing]
[music]
>> When I see [singing] you again.
See you again.
>> [singing]
[music]
[singing]
[applause]
>> This is a new one called Changes, so
it's okay if you don't know it. CJ, you
want to count it off?
>> Three, four.
>> [music]
>> Pedal on that E flat.
[music]
>> Lately, there's [singing] been something
in the air.
>> [music]
>> There's been a lot of smaller talk.
When we were [singing and music]
younger, we would share our fears. Now,
we're afraid [music]
of being alone.
I still can [singing] hear through all
of the silence. [music]
Do you need [singing] any help calling
I did.
There's been some changes
in our life.
I can feel the
distance.
Space and time has
>> [music and singing]
>> made everything different.
Day and night, oh,
everything [music and singing] has
changed and
I don't know
why.
I used to hear [music] your voice inside
my head.
>> [singing]
>> Now, I forget [music] what it sounds
like.
And all the things we used to [singing]
leave unsaid.
Wish [music] they were said [singing] in
hindsight.
I still can hear through
>> [music and singing]
>> all of the silence.
Do you need any help?
Call it like I did.
>> [music]
>> In our life.
>> [singing]
>> I can feel the
distance.
Space [music] and time has made
everything [singing]
different.
Day and night, oh,
everything has changed and
I don't know [music and singing] why.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Maybe that's just the way it is, no
[singing] matter how much I'm missing
[music] it. Sometimes wind blows in
different [singing]
new directions and lessons are
happening. Maybe that's just [singing]
the way it is, no matter how much
[music] I'm missing it. No love lost. I
know it's in a sense what you make of
it. There's been some changes
>> [music]
>> in our life.
I can feel the distance.
Space and [music and singing] time has
made everything different.
Day and night, oh, everything
>> [singing]
[music]
[singing]
[music and singing]
[music]
>> Thank you everybody.
>> [music]
>> One more time
One more time for the band and
everybody.
>> [music]
[music]
>> This is where the end credits roll.
>> [music]
[music]
[applause]
[applause and cheering]
>> Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Wow,
there's so many OF YOU HERE.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
[cheering]
>> THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING. SUPPORT FOR
NPR MUSIC comes from Moises, committed
to ethical innovation and empowering the
creative community with tools for
musicians to master their craft.
A quick update before you go, we're
doing another Tiny Desk giveaway. Enter
by [music] September 12th, 2026 and you
and a friend could win a free trip to DC
to see a Tiny Desk concert live in
person. You even get to choose which
upcoming show you want to see and it's
completely free to enter. Just go to
npr.org/tinydeskgiveaway.
Entering is completely free, but you can
get more entries by snagging some
limited edition Tiny Desk merch or by
making a special donation to the NPR
network. Learn more and enter today at
npr.org/tinydeskgiveaway.